mercedesbenzme.com 2015-04-11

# Privacy Policy | Mercedes-Benz Middle East and Levant - Luxury Passenger Cars

## Privacy Statement

Daimler AG appreciates your interest in its products and your visit to this web site. Your privacy is important to us and we want you to feel comfortable visiting our site. The protection of your privacy in the processing of your personal data is an important concern to which we pay special attention during our business processes. Personal data collected during visits to our web site are processed by us according to the legal provisions valid for the countries in which the web sites are maintained. In addition, our data protection policy complies with the Data Protection Code of Conduct applicable company-wide for Daimler AG. The Daimler AG web site may include, however, links to other web sites which are not covered by this privacy statement.

Download the Daimler Data Protection Code of Conduct

### Collection and Processing of Personal Data

When you visit our web site, our web server automatically records your IP address, the web site from which you visit us, the web pages you actually visit and the date and length of your visit. Personal data is only stored if volunteered by you, for example in the context of a registration, a survey, a contest or in execution of a contract.

### Use and Disclosure of Personal Data and Purpose Specification

Daimler AG will use your personal data for the sole purpose of technical administration of the web site, customer administration, product surveys and marketing, only to the extent necessary in each specific case.

We will only disclose your data to governmental authorities in cases where it is required by law. Our employees, agencies, and retailers are obliged by us to respect confidentiality.

### Freedom of Choice

We should like to use your data to inform you about our products and services and where applicable request your opinion. Naturally your participation is completely voluntary. Should you not consent, you can inform us at any time so that we can suppress your data accordingly. Please refer to the respective web site for further information.

### Cookies

Daimler AG uses cookies to record the preferences of visitors, to enable us to optimize the design of our web site. Cookies are small files which are stored on your hard drive. They ease navigation, and increase the user-friendliness of a web site. Cookies also help us to identify the most popular sections of our web site. This enables us to provide content that is more accurately suited to your needs, and in so doing improve our service. Cookies can be used to determine whether there has been any contact between us and your computer in the past. Only the cookie on your computer is identified. Personal details can be saved in cookies, provided that you have consented to this, for example, in order to facilitate secure online access so that you not need to enter your user ID and password again.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can prevent cookies from being stored on your hard drive by setting your browser to not accept cookies. The exact instructions for this can be found in the manual for your browser. You can delete cookies already on your hard drive at any time. If you choose not to accept cookies, you can still visit our website, however this may result in a reduced availability of the services provided by our web site.

### Security

Daimler AG uses technical and organizational security measures in order to protect the data we have under our control against accidental or intentional manipulation, loss, destruction and against access by unauthorized persons. Our security procedures are continually enhanced as new technology becomes available.

### Freedom of Information

Upon written request, Daimler AG or its representatives will inform you by letter without delay what personal data is stored by us as defined by applicable law. Should such data be incorrect, we will at your request correct that information for you, also as a registered user you have the option of viewing, deleting or amending your personal data yourself. 

Should you have questions regarding the processing of your personal data you can refer to our chief corporate data protection officer, who is also available with his team for enquiries, suggestions or complaints.

Dr. Joachim Riess  
Chief Officer Corporate Data Protection   
Daimler AG  
HPC 0624  
D- 70546 Stuttgart  
Germany

[

##  The all-new A-Class. Drive yourself. 

Find Out More ](http://mercedesbenzme.com/en/sedans-coupes/a-class/) [

##  Enough said. Time to drive it. 

Book a Test Drive ](http://mercedesbenzme.com/en/footer/contact-sales/book-a-test-drive/)
